[{"Date": "2020-07-21 11:57:50+00:00", "question": "South Sudan does not share its border with which one of the following country?\n\u0926\u0915\u094d\u0937\u093f\u0923 \u0938\u0942\u0921\u093e\u0928 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u0926\u0947\u0936 \u0915\u0947 \u0938\u093e\u0925 \u0905\u092a\u0928\u0940 \u0938\u0940\u092e\u093e \u0938\u093e\u091d\u093e \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0915\u0930\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "Kenya", "option2": "Egypt", "option3": "Ethiopia", "option4": "Uganda", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-21 11:57:50+00:00", "question": "How many Dedicated Freight Corridor is India currently have?\n\u0935\u0930\u094d\u0924\u092e\u093e\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092d\u093e\u0930\u0924 \u0915\u0947 \u092a\u093e\u0938 \u0915\u093f\u0924\u0928\u0947 \u0938\u092e\u0930\u094d\u092a\u093f\u0924 \u092b\u094d\u0930\u0947\u091f \u0915\u0949\u0930\u093f\u0921\u094b\u0930 \u0939\u0948\u0902?", "option1": "2", "option2": "4", "option3": "6", "option4": "8", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-21 11:57:50+00:00", "question": "Which of the following Fundamental rights are available to foreigners (except aliens)?\n\u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928 \u0938\u0947 \u092e\u094c\u0932\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u0927\u093f\u0915\u093e\u0930 \u0935\u093f\u0926\u0947\u0936\u093f\u092f\u094b\u0902 (\u090f\u0932\u093f\u092f\u0902\u0938 \u0915\u094b \u091b\u094b\u0921\u093c\u0915\u0930) \u0915\u094b \u0909\u092a\u0932\u092c\u094d\u0927 \u0939\u0948\u0902?", "option1": "Article 15", "option2": "Article 16", "option3": "Article 19", "option4": "Article 20", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-21 11:57:50+00:00", "question": "Under Foreigner registration in India, Pakistani\u00a0nationals visiting India are required to register within what time of their arrival?\n\u092d\u093e\u0930\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0935\u093f\u0926\u0947\u0936\u0940 \u092a\u0902\u091c\u0940\u0915\u0930\u0923 \u0915\u0947 \u0924\u0939\u0924, \u092d\u093e\u0930\u0924 \u0906\u0928\u0947 \u0935\u093e\u0932\u0947 \u092a\u093e\u0915\u093f\u0938\u094d\u0924\u093e\u0928\u0940 \u0928\u093e\u0917\u0930\u093f\u0915\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u094b \u0906\u0917\u092e\u0928 \u0915\u0947 \u0915\u093f\u0924\u0928\u0947 \u0938\u092e\u092f \u0915\u0947 \u092d\u0940\u0924\u0930 \u092a\u0902\u091c\u0940\u0915\u0930\u0923 \u0915\u0930\u0928\u093e \u0906\u0935\u0936\u094d\u092f\u0915 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "Within 12 hours", "option2": "Within 24 hours", "option3": "Within 2 days", "option4": "Within 72 hours", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-21 11:57:50+00:00", "question": "Papikonda National Park\u00a0is located in the state of\n\u092a\u093e\u092a\u0940\u0915\u094b\u0902\u0921\u093e \u0930\u093e\u0937\u094d\u091f\u094d\u0930\u0940\u092f \u0909\u0926\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0928 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u0930\u093e\u091c\u094d\u092f \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u094d\u0925\u093f\u0924 \u0939\u0948", "option1": "Odisha", "option2": "Karnataka", "option3": "Andhra Pradesh", "option4": "Tamil Nadu", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-21 08:12:07+00:00", "question": "The HQ of the The United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR) is located in\n\u0938\u0902\u092f\u0941\u0915\u094d\u0924 \u0930\u093e\u0937\u094d\u091f\u094d\u0930 \u0915\u0947 \u0936\u0930\u0923\u093e\u0930\u094d\u0925\u093f\u092f\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f \u0909\u091a\u094d\u091a\u093e\u092f\u0941\u0915\u094d\u0924 (UNHCR) \u0915\u093e \u092e\u0941\u0916\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0932\u092f \u0938\u094d\u0925\u093f\u0924 \u0939\u0948", "option1": "Geneva, Switzerland", "option2": "Brussels, Belgium", "option3": "Davos, Switzerland", "option4": "Paris, France", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-21 08:12:07+00:00", "question": "Goria, Moria, Desi, Jola is the indigenous muslims of which state?\n\u0917\u094b\u0930\u093f\u092f\u093e, \u092e\u094b\u0930\u093f\u092f\u093e, \u0926\u0947\u0938\u0940, \u091c\u094b\u0932\u093e \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u0930\u093e\u091c\u094d\u092f \u0915\u0947 \u0938\u094d\u0935\u0926\u0947\u0936\u0940 \u092e\u0941\u0938\u0932\u092e\u093e\u0928 \u0939\u0948\u0902?", "option1": "Assam", "option2": "West Bengal", "option3": "Odisha", "option4": "Bihar", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-21 08:12:07+00:00", "question": "Which one of the following archaeological site is found in Tamil Nadu?\n\u0924\u092e\u093f\u0932\u0928\u093e\u0921\u0941 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928 \u0938\u093e \u092a\u0941\u0930\u093e\u0924\u093e\u0924\u094d\u0935\u093f\u0915 \u0938\u094d\u0925\u0932 \u092a\u093e\u092f\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "Doddabetta Peak", "option2": "Adichanallur", "option3": "Sivasagar", "option4": "Salem", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-21 08:12:07+00:00", "question": "Which one of the following is not the regional benches of National Green Tribunal (NGT)?\n\u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928 \u0938\u093e \u0930\u093e\u0937\u094d\u091f\u094d\u0930\u0940\u092f \u0917\u094d\u0930\u0940\u0928 \u091f\u094d\u0930\u093f\u092c\u094d\u092f\u0942\u0928\u0932 (\u090f\u0928\u091c\u0940\u091f\u0940) \u0915\u0947 \u0915\u094d\u0937\u0947\u0924\u094d\u0930\u0940\u092f \u092c\u0947\u0902\u091a \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "Bhopal", "option2": "Pune", "option3": "Chennai", "option4": "Guwahati", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-07-21 08:12:07+00:00", "question": "'Ulsoor Lake' is located in the city of\n'\u0909\u0932\u094d\u0938\u0942\u0930 \u091d\u0940\u0932' \u0907\u0938 \u0936\u0939\u0930 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0939\u0948", "option1": "New Delhi", "option2": "Ahmedabad", "option3": "Bangalore", "option4": "Chennai", "Answer": "No answer given"}]